suchtv.pk 2019-07-18

# PRIVACY POLICY - SUCH TV

This is the main privacy policy for Such TV Internet publications, and for certain services provided through the websites by **SUCH TV**

At Such TV we collect different types of information about our user/visitor/reader and their activities on our website to analyze and better understanding about user/visitor/reader’s interest and issues to improve the services we offer.

There may be additional privacy policies that apply to certain services on Such TV.

### **Our principles**

  * We do our utmost to protect user privacy through the appropriate use of the security technology.

This means: - we ensure that we have appropriate physical and technological security measures to protect your information - we ensure that when we outsource any processes that the service provider has appropriate security measures.

  * We will be transparent in our dealings with you as to what information about you we will collect and how we will use your information.
  * We will use personal data only for the purpose(s) for which they were originally collected and we will ensure personal data are securely disposed of.
  * Our site is accessible via the Internet. This means that, wherever you choose to post your data on the site, they can be accessed from anywhere around the world.

### **What information do we collect?**

We collect following information on our website:

Activates of user/visitor/reader on our website

Submitted CV’s on our Website via e-mail and Carrier panel.

Certain services that we provide may involve the collection by us of additional information, such as your geographic location from time to time, to enable the service to be provided as designed. In particular, this may apply to certain Apps that you download, or which we provide.

### **Use of Cookies**

We use cookies for a number of reasons:

  * For statistical purposes to track how many individual unique users we have and how often they visit our websites. We collect data listing which of our pages are most frequently visited and by which types of users and from which countries.
  * Third party advertisers will generate statistical cookies to track advertising impressions and conversions.
  * Placing cookies on your computer means we can serve you adverts that you might be more interested in, and allows us to control the number of times you see them and measure how effective the ad campaign has been. This helps us to keep the site free of charge.
  * Flash cookies may be used to store user preferences for media player functionality and without them some video content may not render correctly. You can turn cookies off but if you do this you may not be able to use all services on our websites and you might see more pop-ups and other intrusive advertising, as we won't be able to limit what you see using cookies. You will, however, still be able to view editorial content.

By using the sites you are agreeing to the use of cookies as described.

### **Double Click Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our Service. Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our Service or other web sites on the Internet.

You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick Cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the [Google Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/ "Google Ads Settings") web page.

### About our advertising

We use targeted advertising, which allows us to deliver visitors to our website directed to your interests. As you browse suchtv.pk, some of the cookies we place on your computer will be advertising cookies, so we can understand what sort of pages you are interested in. This information we collect about behavior on your computer enables us to group it with computers that show similar behavior. We can then display advertising to your computer, which is based on these interests. For instance if you have been reading a lot of food and drink articles we may decide to show you more adverts for food and drink. We do not share behavioral data with other websites.

### Other Advertising

suchtv.pk will contain contextual affiliate links from which we may earn revenue. Advertisers or affiliates never influence our articles, nor are they written for the purpose of promoting a product, except when clearly branded as a 'sponsored feature' or 'advertisement feature' or 'sponsor's content'.

### **Who we share data with**

We will not share your information with others for marketing purposes unless you have given us your permission.

Please note that we reserve the right to access and disclose personal data to comply with applicable laws and lawful government requests, to operate our systems properly and to protect both our users and ourselves.

Any third parties who access your data in the course of providing services on our behalf are subject to strict contractual restrictions to ensure that your data is protected, and in compliance with applicable data protection/privacy legislation. We may also independently audit these service providers to ensure that they meet our standards. We may use service providers to help us run these site or services available on the sites, some of which may be based outside of Pakistan.

### **Career opportunity**

SUCH TV believes in providing potential candidates with opportunities to explore their relevant field of study, for the said purpose candidates may apply through “Careers” section of our website. The information in the applicants’ resumes is kept secret and treated as highly confidential. “ **Your bio data is safe with us** ”.

### **Changes to the privacy policy**

Should we elect to change our privacy policy we will post the changes here.
